cqcounter.com 2001-06-02

# CQ COUNTER - Free Web Counter, Site Tracker, Online Traffic Reports

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Cybernet Quest will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent. Cybernet Quest may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with Cybernet Quest 's rights or property, other Cybernet Quest users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Cybernet Quest may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. Cybernet Quest shares aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. This data is used to customize Cybernet Quest content and advertising to deliver a better experience for our users. There are cases where Cybernet Quest may ask you for personal information such as your name and email address. We request personal information when you register for an account. Cybernet Quest needs to collect this information for fulfilling prizes, tracking/verifying compliance with Cybernet Quest policies as well as federal, state and local laws and/or for editorial and feedback solicitation purposes. 

**Links to Other Sites**

Users should be aware that when you are on Cybernet Quest pages, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from Cybernet Quest pages that take you outside our service. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While Cybernet Quest strives to protect its user's personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. Cybernet Quest 's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Cybernet Quest 's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. 

**Security**

No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Cybernet Quest can't ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. We make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. Your Cybernet Quest account is password protected so that only you can access it and view the member information relevant to the account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Remember to sign out of your Cybernet Quest account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence. 

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. By registering a account at Cybernet Quest, you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware that our policy may change at any time, although when possible, users will be advised in advance of any changes to the privacy policy. By using this site, you signify your assent to the Cybernet Quest Privacy Policy.
